sopcast.com 2018-12-27

# Disclaimer

What information do we collect when viewing website?

We collect information from you when you register on our web site for broadcasting live channels.  
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may, however, visit our site or use our software anonymously.

What information do we collect when using SopCast client for Windows?

We do not collect any information from you when you use SopCast client to view channels. If you need to broadcast channels from SopCast client, please register yourself on SopCast website first.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

  * To personalize your experience  

  * To improve our website  

  * To improve customer service  

  * To authenticate when broadcast live channels

How do we protect your information?

we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

we do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Non-personally identifiable information may be provided for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through website and not to information collected offline.

You consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

Changes to our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This privacy policy was last modified on 6/20/2009.

Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the email below.

contact@sopcast.com
